{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Basement Finishing Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40128/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40128,"taskName":"Basement - Remodel","taskDescription":"Remodel a Basement","xmTaskDescriptor":"Basement Finishing Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":20,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Basement alter Remodel addition s","textMessagingName":"Remodel Bsmt","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms are general contractors who specialize in finishing or remodeling basements. They supply or coordinate all the relevant services including framing, plumbing, HVAC, electrical, drywall, flooring, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Finish, alter or remodel a basement.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remodel a Basement.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Basement Finishing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Basement Remodeling Contractors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Basement Remodel","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Basement - Remodel","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Basement Remodeling Project","urlName":"Basement-Remodel","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Basement Finishing Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Basement Remodeling Companies","searchKeywords":"egress, Basement, remodel, basements, renovation, remodeling, finish, finished, contractor, general, bar","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":439,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40128/":{"taskOID":40128,"originalTaskOID":40128,"setID":439,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6841,"questionDisplayText":"Basement Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want in your basement? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3475,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Laundry","answerDisplayText":"Laundry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18392,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exercise Area","answerDisplayText":"Exercise Area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9769,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Separate Apartment","answerDisplayText":"Separate Apartment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18394,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Game Room","answerDisplayText":"Game Room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18821,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairway","answerDisplayText":"Stairway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18395,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Home Theater","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6112,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Storage","answerDisplayText":"Storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7120,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5431,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17474,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches of basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional Drawings","answerDisplayText":"Professional Drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6842,"questionDisplayText":"Basement Area Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"My basement is currently:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unfinished","answerDisplayText":"Unfinished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18312,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partially Finished","answerDisplayText":"Partially Finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9771,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Finished","answerDisplayText":"Finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6843,"questionDisplayText":"Square Footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of your basement?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8580,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 400 (small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 400 (small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8581,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"400 - 800 (medium)","answerDisplayText":"400 - 800 (medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8582,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 800 (large)","answerDisplayText":"More than 800 (large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6841,"questionDisplayText":"Basement Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want in your basement? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3475,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Laundry","answerDisplayText":"Laundry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18392,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exercise Area","answerDisplayText":"Exercise Area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9769,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Separate Apartment","answerDisplayText":"Separate Apartment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18394,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Game Room","answerDisplayText":"Game Room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18821,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairway","answerDisplayText":"Stairway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18395,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Home Theater","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6112,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Storage","answerDisplayText":"Storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7120,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3475,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Laundry","answerDisplayText":"Laundry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4335,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Office","answerDisplayText":"Office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18392,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exercise Area","answerDisplayText":"Exercise Area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9769,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Separate Apartment","answerDisplayText":"Separate Apartment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18394,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Game Room","answerDisplayText":"Game Room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18821,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairway","answerDisplayText":"Stairway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18395,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Home Theater","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6112,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Storage","answerDisplayText":"Storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7120,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Workshop","answerDisplayText":"Workshop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5431,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17474,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches of basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional Drawings","answerDisplayText":"Professional Drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17474,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches of basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Professional Drawings","answerDisplayText":"Professional Drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6842,"questionDisplayText":"Basement Area Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"My basement is currently:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unfinished","answerDisplayText":"Unfinished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18312,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partially Finished","answerDisplayText":"Partially Finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9771,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Finished","answerDisplayText":"Finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unfinished","answerDisplayText":"Unfinished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18312,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partially Finished","answerDisplayText":"Partially Finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9771,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Finished","answerDisplayText":"Finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6843,"questionDisplayText":"Square Footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of your basement?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8580,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 400 (small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 400 (small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8581,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"400 - 800 (medium)","answerDisplayText":"400 - 800 (medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8582,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 800 (large)","answerDisplayText":"More than 800 (large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8580,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 400 (small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 400 (small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8581,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"400 - 800 (medium)","answerDisplayText":"400 - 800 (medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8582,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 800 (large)","answerDisplayText":"More than 800 (large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}